Finding Aid for Athletic Department (University of Michigan) records, 1860-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sports Information Office, 1860-
  - Hockey, 1919-
    - Photographs
      - Portraits and Action Photos
        - Digital Photographs and Computer files
          - 2003/04
            - 2003/04 USCH Magazine Cover of Montoya and Tambellini (Box 161)
              (head shots)
            - 2003/04 Headshots, Team, Some Posed (Box 161)
              (File #15716)
            - Ice Hockey Alumni Golf Outing 8/2/2003 (Box 161)
              (photos by Martin Vloet)
            - UM vs. Quinnipiac University 10/18/2003 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Northern Michigan University 10/24/2003 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Northern Michigan University 10/26/2003 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Niagara 11/1/2003 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Wisconsin (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Minnesota (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Michigan State 12/5/2003 (Box 161)
            - Great Lakes Invitational 12/27/2003 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Ohio State 1/9/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Ohio State 1/10/2004 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Lake Superior State University 1/30/2004 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Miami of Ohio 2/13/2004 (Box 161)
            - UM Hockey 2/20/2004 (Box 161)
              (images of UM vs. Bowling Green State University)
            - UM vs. Bowling Green State University 2/20/2004 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Bowling Green State University 2/21/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            - UM vs. University of Nebraska Omaha in first round of CCHA Tournament 3/12/2004 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. University of Nebraska Omaha, CCHA Tournament, First Round, Game 2 3/13/2004 (Box 161)
              (photos by Eric Bronson)
            - UM vs. Northern Michigan in CCHA Super Six, game 1 3/19/2004 (Box 161)
            - UM vs. Northern Michigan in CCHA Super Six, game 2 3/20/2004 (Box 161)
            - NCAA Tournament Northeast Regional, Game 1, UM vs. University of New Hampshire 3/27/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            - CCHA Super Six, UM vs. Northern Michigan and Ohio State 3/19/2004-3/20/2004 (Box 161)
            - NCAA Tournament Northeast Regional, Game 2, UM vs. Boston College 3/28/2004, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            - Deker Banquet 4/17/2004 (Box 161)
            - 2003/04 Ice Hockey Covers (Box 161)
              (images of media guide covers)
              (requires Macintosh computer to open)
            - 2003/04 Ice Hockey Media Guide Inside Covers (Box 161)
            - 2003/04 Media Guide Files and Photos, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
              (articles and photos, including action photos and head shots)
          - 2004/05
            - 2004/05 Media guide files and photos (Box 239)
              (team photos, captain photos, 1955-1956 championship team reunion, game action, NCAA Midwest Regionals, results, box scores, articles, NHL draft, statistics, logos, Yost locker room.)
          - 2005/06
            - 2005/2006 photos and media guide (Box 239)
              (includes files team photos, headshots, incoming freshman files, game action, CCHA playoffs, files, media guide, articles, box scores, weekly releases, articles, poster, CCHA tourney, hockey recruiting)
            - 2005/06 Miscellaneous Photos (Box 239)
              (images of coaches, Dekers, fans, UM band, Yost Arena, and game action photos)
              (photos by Wolverine Photo)
            - 2005/06 Hockey Box Scores (Box 239)
            - 2005/06 Proof sheet of digital photos, 2 folders (Box 239)
              includes facilities, game action, team and group photographs, crowd shots)
          - 2006/07
            - Proof sheets of digital photographs, 3 folders (Box 239)
              (includes locker room and Yost arena shots, Yost construction, team photos, game action, senior's night)
            - Digital photos on CD/DVD, 1 folders (Box 239)
          - 2007/08
            - Proof sheets of digital files, 4 folders (Box 239)
              (includes team photos, group photos, mock rock, game action, CCHA playoff, crowd shots, net perspective shots, locker room and facilities)
            - Digital photos files on CDs/DVDs, 1 folders (Box 239)
              (includes Yost construction and renovation, team photos, game action, record book, NCAA playoffs, Frozen Four, Michigan awards at Fox theatre, results and bios, statistics, CCHA All Access Show #9 aired 3/21/2008 and CSTV DVD featuring Yost Arena history and interviews with player and Red Berenson)
          - 2008/09 (Box 240)
            - Proof sheets of digital files, 5 folders (Box 240)
              (includes headshots, team photos, group photos, game action)
      - Miscellaneous and Undated Photographs
        - Dekers Hall of Fame Photos (Box 15)
          (selection of oversize reprints formerly hanging in Yost Arena, selected only those not found elsewhere in BHL collections, Most have short "bio" tape or pasted to image. Includes Neil Celley, Ross Childs, Willard Ikola, Lorne Howes, John MacInnes, Gordon MacMillen, Joe Marmo, John Matchefts, Doug Mullen, John Palenstein, Ross Smith, Wally Grant, Al Renfrew, John Sherf, Gordon Wilkie, Doug Barnett, Howard Colby, Lois Issacson, Glen Williams)
        - NCAA championship photo 1996 (Box 15)
        - 1991/92 players (Box 15)
          (collectors cards, uncut)
        - Game Action, misc., (prints) (Box 15)
        - Reunion team photo, ca 1980-1985 (Box 15)
          (includes Red Berenson)
    - Miscellaneous
      - NCAA Championship Scoresheets 1996, 1998 (Box 15)
        (mounted)
      - 1919/1920 Informal Hockey Team (Box 15)
        (clippings about club hockey team and prospects for hockey becoming a varsity sport)
      - Biographical sketches of All-Americans and coach Vic Heyliger (Box 15)
        (photocopies of captions from Yost Arena photos)
      - Hobey Baker Award 1996 (Box 15)
      - Hockey Reunion 1998 (Box 15)
      - U.S. Senate Resolution honoring 1996 NCAA champions April 15, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Game Programs
      - 1945-1947 (Box 36)
      - 1959/60-1965/66 (Box 36)
      - 1966/67-1971/72 (Box 36)
      - 1972/73-1973/74 (Box 36)
      - 1974/75 (Box 36)
      - 1975/76 (Box 36)
      - 1976/77 (Box 36)
      - 1977/78 (Box 36)
      - 1978/79 (Box 36)
      - 1979/80 (Box 36)
      - 1980/81 (Box 36)
      - 1981/82 (Box 36)
      - 1982/83 (Box 36)
      - 1983/84 (Box 36)
      - 1984/85 (Box 36)
      - 1985/86 (Box 36)
      - 1986/87 (Box 36)
      - 1987/88 (Box 36)
      - 1988/89 (Box 36)
      - 1989/90 (Box 36)
      - 1990/91 (Box 36)
      - 1991/92 (Box 36)
      - 1992/93 (Box 37)
      - 1993/94 (Box 37)
      - 1994/95 (Box 37)
      - 1995/96 (Box 37)
      - 1996/97 (Box 37)
      - 1997/98 (Box 37)
      - 1998/99 (Box 37)
      - 1999/00 (Box 102)
      - 2000/01 (Box 102)
      - 2001/02 (Box 102)
      - 2002/03 (Box 102)
      - 2004/05 (Box 102)
      - 2005/06 (Box 102)
      - 2006//07 (Box 102)
      - 2007/08 (Box 102)
      - 2003/04 (Box 10)
      - 2004/05 (Box 10)
      - 2005/06 (Box 10)
      - 2006/07 (Box 10)
      - 2010-2013 (Box 102)
    - Game Results and Statistics
      - 1922/23-1929/30 (Box 167)
      - 1930/31-1939/40 (Box 167)
      - 1940/41-1949/50 (Box 167)
      - 1950/51-1959/60 (Box 167)
      - 1960/61-1964/65 (Box 167)
      - 1965/66 Box Scores (Box 167)
      - 1966/67 Box Scores (Box 167)
      - 1967/68 Game Summaries (Box 167)
      - 1968/69 Box Scores (Box 167)
      - 1969/70 (Box 167)
      - 1970/71 (Box 167)
      - 1971/72 Box Scores (Box 167)
      - 1972/73 (Box 167)
      - 1973/74 Game Summaries (Box 167)
      - 1974/75 Game Summaries (Box 167)
      - 1975/76 Game Summaries (Box 167)
      - 1976/77, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - 1977/78 Game Summaries (Box 167)
      - 1978/79, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - 1979/80, 3 folders (Box 167)
      - 1980/81 (Box 167)
      - 1981/82 (Box 168)
      - 1981/82 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - 1982/83, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - 1983/84 (Box 168)
      - 1983/84 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - 1984/85 (Box 168)
      - 1984/85 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - 1985/86 (Box 168)
      - 1985/86 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - 1986/87 (Box 168)
      - 1986/87 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - 1987/88 (Box 168)
      - 1987/88 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - 1988/89 (Box 169)
      - 1988/89 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 169)
      - 1989/90 (Box 169)
      - 1989/90 Game Summaries, 2 folders (Box 169)
      - 1990/91, 2 folders (Box 169)
      - 1990/91 Game Summaries (Box 169)
      - 1991/92 Game Summaries (Box 169)
      - 1992/93 CCHA Final Statistics (Box 169)
      - 1992/93 Game Summaries (Box 169)
      - 1993/94, 3 folders (Box 170)
      - 1993/94 Game Summaries (Box 170)
      - 1994/95, 2 folders (Box 170)
      - 1994/95 Game Summaries (Box 170)
      - 1995/96, 4 folders (Box 170)
      - 1995/96 Game Notes and Line Charts, Part 1 (Box 171)
      - 1995/96 Game Notes and Line Charts, Part 2 (Box 171)
      - 1995/96 Game Summaries (Box 171)
      - 1996/97, 9 folders (Box 171)
      - 1996/97 Game Notes and Line Charts (Box 172)
      - 1996/97 Game Summaries (Box 172)
      - 1997/98, 6 folders (Box 172)
      - 1997/98 Game Notes and Line Charts (Box 172)
      - 1997/98 Game Summaries (Box 172)
      - 1998/99, 5 folders (Box 173)
      - 1998/99 Game Notes and Line Charts (Box 173)
      - 1998/99 Game Summaries (Box 173)
      - 1999/00, 5 folders (Box 173)
      - 1999/00 Game Notes and Line Charts (Box 173)
      - 1999/00 Game Summaries (Box 174)
      - 2000/01, 4 folders (Box 174)
      - 2000/01 Game Notes and Line Charts (Box 174)
      - 2000/01 Game Summaries (Box 174)
      - 2001/02 Game Notes and Line Charts, October-December, 2001 (Box 174)
      - 2001/02 Game Notes and Line Charts, January-April, 2002 (Box 174)
      - 2001/02 Game Summaries (Box 174)
      - 2001/02 Season in Review (Box 174)
      - 2001/02 Final Player Bios (Box 175)
      - 2002/03 Game Notes and Line Charts, October-December, 2002 (Box 175)
      - 2002/03 Game Notes and Line Charts, January-April, 2003 (Box 175)
      - 2002/03 Game Summaries (Box 175)
      - 2002/03 Season in Review (Box 175)
      - 2003/04 Game Summaries (Box 175)
      - 2003/04 Season in Review (Box 175)
      - 2004/05 Box Scores and Line Charts (Box 175)
      - 2004/05 Season in Review (Box 175)
      - 2005/06 Box Scores, Shot Charts, Line Charts (Box 175)
      - 2008/09 Box Scores, Shot Charts, Line Charts (Box 175)
    - Articles
      - 1992/93 (Box 176)
      - 1995/96 Feature Articles (Box 176)
      - 1995/96 NCAA Title Run Clippings (Box 176)
      - 1995/96 Overall Program Clippings, 2 folders (Box 176)
      - 1995/96 Weekly Articles (Box 176)
      - 1996/97 Feature Articles, 2 folders (Box 176)
      - 1996/97 NCAA Tournament Sections (Box 176)
      - 1997/98 Team Articles, 2 folders (Box 176)
      - 1998/99 Clippings, 4 folders (Box 176)
      - 1999/2000 Clippings, 1 folders (Box 176)
      - 2000/01 Newspaper Articles (Box 176)
      - 2001/02 Newspaper Articles, June-December, 2001 (Box 176)
      - 2001/02 Newspaper Articles, January-April, 2002 (Box 177)
      - 2001/02 Minnesota Newspapers, 4/5/2002 (Box 177)
      - 2002/03 Newspaper Articles, Preseason and September-December, 2002 (Box 177)
      - 2002/03 Newspaper Articles, January-March, 2003 and Postseason (Box 177)
      - 2002/03 The Coin Toss, UM vs. MSU (Box 177)
      - 2003/04 (Box 177)
      - 2004/05 Preseason Articles (includes American Hockey Magazine article on Michigan Fans at Yost) (Box 177)
      - 2004/05 Articles, September-December, 2004, January-May, 2005 (Box 177)
      - 2004/05 The Wolverine, 3/21/2005 (Box 177)
      - 2005/06 Articles (Box 177)
      - Michigan Daily National Champions Special edition, January 5-6, 1998 (Folder 8)
    - Releases
      - 1992/93 Dekers Releases (Box 178)
      - 1992/93 Weekly Releases (Box 178)
      - 1995/96 Weekly Releases (Box 178)
      - 1996/97, 2 folders (Box 178)
      - 1996/97 75th Anniversary All-Time Team (Box 178)
      - 1996/97 News Releases/Information (Box 178)
      - 1997/98 CCHA Releases (Box 178)
      - 1997/98 Press Releases (Box 178)
      - 1998/99 Weekly Releases (Box 178)
      - 2001/02 UM vs. MSU Cold War Releases (Box 178)
      - 2003 NCAA Ice Hockey Midwest Regional (Box 178)
        (see box 161 for digital material)
  - Lacrosse
    - Results and Miscellaneous 2012 (Box 286)
  - Soccer -- Men
    - Media Guides
      - 1998/99 (Box 213)
      - 2000 (Box 213)
      - 2001/02 (Box 213)
      - 2003/04 (Box 213)
      - 2005/06-2006/07 (Box 213)
      - 2007/08-2008/09 (Box 213)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photographs
        - 2000 (Box 213)
        - 2001 (Box 213)
        - 2002 (Box 213)
        - 2003, thumbnails of digital photos (Box 213)
        - 2004, thumbnails of digital photos (Box 213)
      - Portraits and Action Shots
        - 2000 (Box 213)
          - Compiled player action shots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
          - Game action, contact sheets of Photos Services negs (Box 213)
          - First game, 1 cd (Box 213)
        - 2001
          - 2001 Media guide images and files, 1 cd (Box 213)
          - Compiled player action, 1 cd (Box 213)
          - Northwestern 9/24/2001, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
            (Amir Gamzu)
          - Indiana 10/7/2001, 1 cd (Box 213)
        - 2002
          - 2002 Season Files and Media guide, 2 optical disks cds (Box 213)
          - Team Photo and Player headshots, 2 optical disks cds (Box 213)
          - Compiled player action, 2 optical disks cds (Box 213)
          - Compiled player action photos, 1 cd (Box 213)
            (by Amir Gamzu, Martin Vloet,Brad Mills)
          - Akron 8/24/2002, contact sheets and 1 cd with MSU and OSU (Box 213)
            (Photo Services, selections from contact sheets)
          - IUPUI 9/6/2002, 1 cd (Box 213)
          - Yale 9/15/2002, contact sheets, 1 cd (Box 213)
          - Bowling Green 10/9/2002, 1 cd (Box 213)
            (Amir GaAmzu)
          - Michigan State 10/13/2002, contact sheets (Box 213)
          - Ohio State 11/3/2002, contact sheets (Box 213)
          - Oakland 11/9/2002, 1 (Box 213)
          - Michigan State 10/13/2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
            (Brad Mills)
        - 2003
          - Dayton 9/5/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
          - Evansville 9/7/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
          - Indiana 10/5/2003, 1 cd (Box 213)
          - Michigan State 10/12/2003, 1 cd, partial contact sheets (Box 213)
          - Northwestern 10/17/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
          - Wisconsin, 10/92003, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
          - St Peters, NCAA 11/26/2003, 2 optical disks contact sheet, cds (Box 213)
          - St. Peters, NCAA 11/26/2003, 2 optical disks contact sheet, cds (Box 213)
            (Martin Vloet)
          - Santa Clara NCAA 12/06/2003, contact sheet (Box 213)
        - 2004
          - Game action, 10 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
            (Wolverine Photo)
          - Head shots and Team photo, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
            (UM Photo Services)
          - Media guide, releases etc., 1 optical disks CDs (Box 213)
        - 2005 (game action, team photos, post-season), 1 volumes contact sheets & digital files (CDs (Box 233)
        - 2006 (game action, team photos, post-season), 1 volumes contact sheets & digital files (CDs (Box 233)
        - 2007 (community service, kid clinic, team photos, head shots, game action, Special Olympics), 1 volumes contact sheets & digital files (CDs) (Box 233)
        - 2008 (game action, team photos, headshots. senior day, Big 10 Tournament), contact sheets & digital files (CDs (Box 233)
      - Portraits and Action Shots
        - 2009 (team, headshots, compiled player game action, game action (vs Xavier only) (Box 213)
        - 2010 (DVD of Big Ten tournament and NCAA 1st round vs. USC) (Box 213)
    - Meet Programs and Results
      - 2000 (Box 214)
      - 2001, 2 folders (Box 214)
      - 2002, 2 folders (Box 214)
      - 2003, 2 folders (Box 214)
      - 2004, 2 folders (Box 214)
    - Press Releases and Clippings
      - 2000 (Box 214)
      - 2001 (Box 214)
      - 2002 (Box 214)
      - 2003 (Box 214)
      - 2004 (Box 214)
    - Meet Programs
      - 2012 (Box 214)
    - Big Ten / NCAA
      - Big Ten Statistics 2000 (Box 214)
      - Big Ten Statistics 2001 (Box 214)
      - Big Ten / NCAA tournament programs 2002-2004 (Box 214)
    - Results and Statistics
      - 2009 (Box 284)
      - 2010 (Box 284)
    - Programs and Post-Season Guides
      - 2008 (Box 284)
      - 2009 (Box 284)
      - 2010 (Box 284)
    - Press Releases and Articles
      - 2010 (Box 284)
  - Swimming-men
    - Media Guides, 1938-
      - 1938-1942, 1944-1946 (Box 42)
      - 1950-1952, 1954, 1956, 1958-1959 (Box 42)
      - 1960-1968 (Box 42)
      - 1969-1972 (Box 42)
      - 1973/74-1985/86 (Box 42)
      - 1987/88-1991/92 (Box 42)
      - 1992/93-1993/94 (Box 42)
      - 1994/95-1995/96 (Box 42)
      - 1996/97-1998/99- (Box 42)
      - 1999/00-2000/01 (Box 42)
      - 2001/02-2002/03 (Box 42)
      - 2003/04-2004/05 (Box 42)
      - 2005/06-2006/07 (Box 42)
    - Meet Programs and Results
      - 1889 AAU 2nd Western Championship (Box 42)
      - 1931-1945 (Box 42)
      - 1947-1958 (Box 42)
      - 1960 (50th Western Conference Meet) (Box 42)
      - 1963-1967 (Box 42)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 42)
      - 1970 (Box 42)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 42)
      - 1973 (Box 42)
      - 1973/74 (Box 42)
      - 1974/75 (Box 42)
      - 1975/76 (Box 42)
      - 1976/77-1977/78 (Box 42)
      - 1978/79-1979/80 (Box 42)
      - 1980/81 (Box 42)
      - 1981/82 (Box 120)
      - 1982/83 (Box 120)
      - 1983/84 (Box 120)
      - 1984/85 (Box 120)
      - 1985/86 (Box 120)
      - 1986/87 (Box 120)
      - 1987/88 (Box 120)
      - 1988/89 (Box 120)
      - 1989/90, 2 folders (Box 120)
      - 1990/91, 4 folders (Box 120)
      - 1991/92 (Box 120)
      - 1992/93, 3 folders (Box 120)
      - 1993/94, 4 folders (Box 121)
      - 1994/95, 3 folders (Box 121)
      - 1996 Olympic Trials (Box 121)
      - 1996/97, 4 folders (Box 121)
      - 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 121)
      - 1998/99, 3 folders (Box 121)
      - 1999/00, 2 folders (Box 179)
      - 2000 Olympic trials (Box 179)
      - 2000/01, 4 folders (Box 179)
      - 2001/02, 4 folders (Box 179)
      - 2002/03
        - Results, 2 folders (Box 179)
        - Media Guide Supplement (Box 179)
        - Big Ten and NCAA Championships Programs (Box 179)
        - News and Post Event Releases (Box 179)
        - Weekly Releases (Box 179)
        - Articles (Box 179)
      - 2003/04 (Box 219)
        - Results, 2 folders (Box 219)
        - Big Ten Championships Program (Box 219)
        - News and Post Event Releases (Box 219)
        - Weekly Releases (Box 219)
        - 2004 Olympics, Releases and Articles (Box 219)
      - 2004/05
        - Season Recap (Box 219)
        - Big Ten and NCAA Media Guide Supplements (Box 219)
        - Programs (Box 219)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos
        - Prints
          - 1945, 1946, 1948, 1953, 1954, 1960, 1961, 1964, 1966, 1970, 1972, 1973, 1974, 1979, 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984 (Box 43)
          - 1985 1987-2001/02 (Box 43)
          - 2002/03-2003/04 (Box 43)
          - 1920 (informal team), 1940, 1941, 1943, 1947 (Box 14)
        - Negatives 2000/01 (Box 43)
      - Portraits and Action Photographs
        - 1926-1927 (Box 43)
        - 1930-1939 (Box 43)
        - 1940-1949 (Box 43)
        - 1950-1954 (Box 43)
          (includes photos of Matt Mann and Burwell Jones at 1952 Olympics)
        - 1955-1959 (Box 43)
        - 1960-1963 (Box 43)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 43)
        - 1966-1968 (Box 43)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 43)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 43)
        - 1972/73-1974/75 (Box 43)
        - 1975/76 (Box 43)
        - 1976/77 (Box 43)
        - 1977/78 (Box 43)
        - 1978/79-1979/80 (Box 43)
        - 1980/81 (Box 43)
        - 1981/82 (Box 43)
        - 1982/83 (Box 43)
        - 1983/84 (Box 43)
        - 1984/85 (Box 43)
        - 1985/86 (Box 43)
        - 1991/92 (Box 43)
        - 1991/92 (Box 43)
        - 1992/93 (Box 43)
        - 1993/94 (Box 43)
        - 1994/95 (Box 43)
        - 1996 Tom Dolan at Olympics (Box 43)
        - 1989-1996 portraits and action shots of U-M Olympians (Box 43)
        - 1996/97 (Box 43)
        - 1997/98 (Box 43)
        - 1998/99 (Box 43)
        - 1999/00 (Box 43)
        - 2000/01 (Box 43)
          (see box 161 for additional digital photographs)
        - 2001/02-2002/03 (b/w contact sheets from digital photos) (Box 219)
        - 2002/03 (Box 219)
          (cs, meet action)
        - 2003/04 (Box 219)
          (cs, head shots, meet action)
        - 2003/04 (Box 219)
          (prints, posed)
        - 2004/05 (Box 219)
          (cs, head shots, meet action, includes photos of Michael Phelps)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Copy Negatives and Slide of Historical Swimming Photos (Box 219)
          - Michigan Athletes in International Swimming Hall of Fame (Box 219)
          - Unidentified or Undated Photographs (Box 219)
        - Kent Ferguson (Box 219)
      - Digital Files
        - 1981/82-1984/85, 1986/87-1992/93 Team Photos (Box 161)
          (compilation of scanned images)
        - 2000/01-2001/02
          - 2000/01 Guide (Box 161)
            (photographs, headshots; doc files of player biographies and results)
          - 2001/02, 4 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            (vs Indiana, NCAA meet and unidentified action)
          - 2001/02, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
            (vs Purdue, 1/7/2002 ?)
          - 2001/02 Swim Head Shots (Box 161)
            (photographs, head shots, team)
          - 2001/02 Men's Media Guide (Box 161)
            (pdf files of media guide)
          - 2001/02 Swimming Etc. (Box 161)
            (photographs, head shots and posed)
          - 2001/02 Michigan Men Swimming (Box 161)
            (photographs, meet action)
        - 2002/03
          - 2002/03 UM vs. Northwestern (Box 161)
          - 2002/03 Big Ten Championships, Day 1 and 2 (Box 161)
          - 2002/03 Big Ten Championships, Day 3 (Box 161)
          - 2002/03 NCAA Championships (Box 161)
          - 2002/03 SDM Season (Box 161)
            (photographs, head shots, meet action and team; excel, pdf, and doc files of releases, media guide, and statistics)
          - 2002/03 Men's Swimming (Box 161)
            (photographs, head shots)
          - 2002/03 Swim Guide and Other (Box 161)
            (photographs, head shots, meet action, team; pdf files of media guide)
          - 2002/03 MSD Guide (Box 161)
            (pdf file of media guide)
          - 2002/03 Men's Swim Guide Covers, eps files of media guide covers and doc files of schedules and notes of guide content, eps files will only open on Mac OS (Box 161)
          - 2002/03 Men's Swim Guide Covers (Box 161)
            (copy migrated from eps format to tiff format)
        - 2003/04
          - 2003/04 UM vs. Michigan State University (Box 161)
            (photos, meet action)
          - 2003/04 UM vs. Texas (Box 161)
          - 2003/04 UM vs. Stanford, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 161)
          - 2003/04 UM vs. Eastern Michigan University (Box 161)
            (cs, photographs, meet action)
          - 2003/04 Head Shots (Box 161)
            (photographs, b/w head shots)
          - 2003/04 Head Shots (Box 161)
            (photographs, color head shots, posed)
            (includes photos of women swimming team trophy presentation)
            (by Martin Vloet)